{
   "response_code":0,
   "results":[
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"What AOP stands for",
         "correct_answer":"Aspect Oriented Programming",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Aspect Oriented Programming",
            "Any Object Programming",
            "Asset Oriented Programming",
            "Asset Oriented Protocol"

         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"Which of the following stands true for spring beans?",
         "correct_answer":"All of the above.",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Spring beans are managed by the Spring IoC container.",
            "Spring beans are instantiated, assembled, and otherwise managed by a Spring IoC container.",
            "Spring beans are simple POJOs.",
            "All of the above."
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"What is global-session scope?",
         "correct_answer":"This scopes the bean definition to HTTP Session.",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "This scopes a bean definition to an HTTP Application/ Global session.",
            "This scopes the bean definition to Spring IoC container.",
            "This scopes the bean definition to HTTP request.",
            "This scopes the bean definition to HTTP Session."
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"How do you turn on annotation wiring?",
         "correct_answer":"Add <context:annotation-config/> to bean configuration.",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Add <annotation-context:config /> to bean configuration.",
            "Add <annotation-config /> to bean configuration.",
            "Add <annotation-context-config /> to bean configuration.",
            "Add <context:annotation-config/> to bean configuration."
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What is ContextStartedEvent event?",

         "correct_answer":"ContextStartedEvent event is published when the ApplicationContext is started using the start() method on the ConfigurableApplicationContext interface.",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "This event is published when the Servlet Context is either initialized or refreshed.",
            "This event is published when the HTTP Request is received.",
            "This event is published when the ApplicationContext is started using the start() method on the ConfigurableApplicationContext interface.",
            "This event is published when the HTTP Response is returned."
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"What is Target object?",
         "correct_answer":"The object being advised by one or more aspects, this object will always be a proxy object, also referred to as the advised object.",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "A represents a object in your application where you can plug-in AOP aspect.",
            "The object being advised by one or more aspects, this object will always be a proxy object, also referred to as the advised object.",
            "This is used to inject values in objects",
            "This is not invoked during program execution by Spring AOP framework."
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"How to get object of a service in spring framework?",
         "correct_answer":"Using new keyword",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Using new keyword",
            "Using dependency injection",
            "Using Constructor"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"What is the scope of stateful bean?",
         "correct_answer":"prototype",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "session",
            "global-session",
            "prototype",
            "request"
         ]
      },

      {
        "category":"General Knowledge",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"What are the features of Spring Boot?",
        "correct_answer":"Above of ALL",
        "incorrect_answers":[
           "Web Development",
           "SpringApplication",
           "Application events and listeners",
           "Above of ALL"
        ]
     },

     
     {
        "category":"General Knowledge",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Spring-WS provides various abstract endpoint classes for you to process the request.",
        "correct_answer":"org.springframework.ws.server.endpoint",
        "incorrect_answers":[
           "org.springframework.ws.server.endpoint",
           "org.springframework.ws.server",
           "org.springframework.*",
           "none of the mentioned"
        ]
     },

     {
        "category":"General Knowledge",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Endpoint Classes for DOM:-",
        "correct_answer":"AbstractDomPayloadEndpoint",
        "incorrect_answers":[
           "AbstractDomPayloadEndpoint",
           "AbstractJDomPayloadEndpoint",
           "AbstractDom4jPayloadEndpoint",
           " AbstractXomPayloadEndpoint"
        ]
     },

     {
        "category":"General Knowledge",
        "type":"multiple",
        "difficulty":"easy",
        "question":"Endpoint Classes for dom4j:-",
        "correct_answer":"AbstractDomPayloadEndpoint",
        "incorrect_answers":[
           "AbstractDomPayloadEndpoint",
           "AbstractJDomPayloadEndpoint",
           "AbstractDom4jPayloadEndpoint",
           "AbstractXomPayloadEndpoint"
        ]
     }
     
   ]
}